Muhamad Elhadedy

UX / UI Designer

Cairo. Egypt.

Contact

+201554215707

Muhamadelhadedy@gmail.com

Muhamad Elhadedy_

Bē Muhamad Elhadedy_

in

Muhamad Elhadedy_

About Me

I'm UI/UX Designer with a great experience. I'm trying to make innovative and meaningful designs to make user experience and usability attractive and friendly. I enjoy solving problems by turning them into simple but elegant UX designs.

Skills

- UX UI Design
- Web Design
- Mobile App Design
- Wirframing
- Information Architecture
- User Flow
- User Stories
- Competitive Analysis
- Heuristic Evaluation Analysis

Education & Cerifications

2013 - 2018

Science Valley Academy

Civil Engineering

Jan 2022 - Feb 2022

UX Design

Edraak

Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

ITI/KFS

UI/UX Design

Languages

English - Conversational

Arabic - Native

Experience

Feb 2021 - Present

UX/UI Designer/ Freelance Designer

March 2021 - May 2022

UX UI Designer (Full -Time)

Links

May 2022 - July 2023

UX UI Designer (Full -Time)

Kian

Dec 2022 - March 2024

UX UI Designer (Full -Time)

Bit68

July 2023 - Dec 2023

UX UI Designer (Part -Time)

Trend

July 2023 - Present

(Full -Time) **Product Designer**

Depo

I have worked with a lot of clients from all over the world created websites, mobile apps, interaction and dashboards design.

Tools

Figma

Abode Illustrator